怎么了
What?
咱们这是日行一善 好不好
It's our good deed for the day, all right?
省省吧 兄弟 我来搞定
Slow your roll, bro. I got it.
- 到了  - 谢谢你
- All right.  - Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
我发誓 在刚才问路的时候
I swear, when I asked for directions,
绝没料到会载我一程
I never expected a ride.
或者说 是一趟观光游
Or a guided tour, I bet.
这是我们的荣幸 真的
Well, it was our pleasure. It really was.
希望你在随后的纽约之行开心
I hope you enjoy the rest of your stay in New York.
那么 如果你还需要其他
Now, if you need anything--
任何帮助 给我打电话就行 知道吗
That's anything-- just call me, okay?
人们都说纽约人特别粗鲁
And they say New Yorkers are so rude.
真是胡说八道 你们俩太赞了
- Crazy. - You guys are awesome.
谢谢啦 拜拜
Thank you. Bye.
再见
Bye.
喔
Ooh.
贴心警官 准备好重返工作岗位了吗
Officer Sweetie Pie, are you ready to get back to work?
还没 我快饿死了
No. I'm starving.
就在街那边 有家特棒的日本料理店
There's this great Japanese fusion place right up the street.
咱俩一起去那儿吃午饭吧
Put us out for lunch.
你刚把咱们整个午饭时间用光了
You just used up our entire meal period.
1C线广播 一则报案称
One Charles on the air, be advised you have a 911 call
有人持枪出现在华盛顿广场公园
Of a man with a gun in Washington Square Park.
男子 白人 三十多岁 身着灰色西装和领带 深色头发
Male white, 30s, wearing a gray suit and tie dark hair.
开工
Let's do it.
我真的快饿死了
I'm really starving.
这叫报应 兄弟
That's karma, bro.
我要饿扁了
I'm really hungry.
我不知道哪儿才算中间立场 议员先生
I'm not sure where that middle ground would be, Councilman.
在你看来一天工作12小时才能不断创造财富
You see a 12-hour workday creating economies;
而我看到的是三万四千名警员因疲惫无法全心工作
I see 34,000 tired cops unable to perform at their optimum.
彼此彼此
Likewise.
抱歉
Sorry.
我才该道歉 我知道你很忙
No, I'm sorry; I know you're busy.
对你再忙也有时间
Not for you.
我到底该怎么对付你的上级
How the hell do I handle your boss?
市长今天在法庭上失态了吗
The mayor didn't behave himself in court today?
他的竞选顾问
His campaign consultant
从他的再竞选基金里
embezzles a quarter of a million dollars
挪用了二十五万美元
from his reelection fund.
市长是我的重要证人 但他却没出庭
The mayor is my star witness, and he's a no-show.
他说原因了吗
Did he say why?
市里的紧急公务
Urgent city business.
我们总有这种情况呀
We've been known to have that.
要是真有那么紧急 你就应该知道是什么事
If it was that urgent, you would have known about it.
看样子他并不愿意在宣誓后被提问
It sounds like he didn't want to be questioned under oath.
是的
Yeah.
你觉得是怎么回事
What's that tell you?
我觉得他有一些事没有告诉我
That there's something he's not telling me.
如果他拒绝作证
If he refuses to testify...
你有传讯他的权力
You have subpoena power.
传讯咱们的上级吗
Subpoena our mutual boss?
结局必定双输
Talk about a lose-lose.
荣誉属于那些有真才实干的人
The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena,
即使他失败了 至少他勇敢地去尝试了
who, at worst, if he fails... fails while daring greatly.
说得好
Nice words.
这不是我说的 是罗斯福局长说的
They're not mine, they're Commissioner Roosevelt's.
看样子根本没人在乎
Nobody seems too concerned
有一个持枪的疯子正在这儿晃悠
About a crazed gunman on the loose.
哪边走
Which way?
如果这是个报假警的话咱就去吃饭吧
To lunch, if this is 90-X.
这不是咱能做主的 文 拜托
Not our call, Vin. Come on.
好吧
Fine.
你往右走 我往左走
You go right; I'll go left.
这样不太好吧
Not a good idea.
咱们一人一半省时间
Hey, twice the ground, half the time.
要是你发现了什么可疑情况 就呼叫我
Put it over the air if you see anything.
真抱歉我迟到了
I'm so sorry I'm late.
我差点就不等你了
I was just about to give up on you.
文 你听得到吗
Vin, you on the air?
文 听见了吗
Hey, Vin, you on the air?
女士 麻烦你离开这儿
Ma'am, I need you to exit the park, please.
这边 谢谢
This way. Thanks.
你个渣滓 狗娘养的
Piece of garbage son of a bitch!
先生 把双手放在我能看见的地方
Sir, I need to see your hands right now.
- 你想看我的手 是吗  - 露出手来
- Oh, you want to see my hands? Huh?  - Show me your hands.
- 手在这儿呢  - 把枪扔了
- Here's my hands.  - Hey, drop the gun!
- 你以为我怕你吗  - 马上把枪扔掉
- You think I'm a coward?  - Drop the gun right now!
把它放在地上
Put it on the ground!
放下
Drop it!
别做傻事
Don't do it!
呼叫总部  请马上派辆救护车过来
Central, we need a bus forthwith at this location.
出了什么事
What happened?
注意 这是一起警员枪击案
Be advised, this is a police-involved shooting.
请另派支援小组和一名督导员
Requesting 10-85 and a supervisor...
你没事吧
Are you okay?
■
监制:  基贝勒  跨将军
翻译:  汆汆  POPO  兰夕张
■
翻译:   杜克  基帝  游
校对:  小刀噗噗盟
■
时间轴:  Tiger    后期:  A.PN
第三季.第十一集
警 察 世 家
我知道你这是第一次 孩子 但是还得按流程来
I know it's your first time, kid, but, uh, here's the drill.
没收我的枪 做弹道检查
Confiscate my gun, run ballistics,
确保一切合法
make sure everything's copacetic.
同时 我可以使用非当班武器
In the meantime, I'm free to use my off-duty weapon.
根据规章 你会被分配到行政岗位
As per protocol, you'll be placed on administrative duty...
值班三次 我明白
Three tours; I got it.
警官 我很感谢你的关心
Sarge... look, I appreciate the hand-holding,
但是我想尽快接受
but I'd like to get my interview
枪击审查部门的调查 如果可以的话
with the shooting team over with, if that's okay.
不可以 你下一步应该是
No, it's not okay. The next step is,
去医院接受心理创伤检查
you go to the hospital and get checked out for trauma.
没必要 警官
It's not necessary, Sarge.
每个警察枪击后都得接受检查 不管是什么情况
Every cop goes after every shooting, fatal or not.
在医生通过你的审核之前
And the investigator isn't allowed to talk to you
你不能接受调查人员的讯问
till the doc clears you.
我没做错 我根本没得选
I didn't do anything wrong; he didn't give me a choice.
真是疯了
It was crazy.
这就是我要说的 明白吗
That's what I'm talking about, right?
自我怀疑开始一点点侵入你的头脑
Little self-doubts start creeping in.
接受检查可以让你头脑变得清醒
This way, it gives you time to clear your head.
好的
Yeah,
所以 你不要说些傻话
so you don't go saying something stupid
像是 “我没必要开枪打他的”
like, "Well, I didn't have to shoot him."
嘿 丹尼 你在这儿干什么
Hey, Danny, what are you doing here?
虽然我说了不算 但我还是觉得
It's not my call, but I don't think
他们不会让你接手这个案子的 雷根
they're gonna allow you to work this one, Reagan.
我只是来看看我弟弟 警官
I'm just checking up on my kid brother, Sarge.
要是风纪组谁有意见的 可以来咬我啊
If anyone at IA got a problem with it, they can bite me.
你还好吧
You okay?
嗯 我没事 我没得选
Yeah, I'm fine. He didn't give me a choice.
好 听你头儿的话 好吗
All right, well, listen to your boss, okay?
去医院吧
Now, get to the hospital.
去圣维克医院吧 琳达今天值班
In fact, go to St. Vic's. Linda's working.
好的
Yeah, okay.
要搭车什么的吗
You need a ride or anything?
不了 我没事
No, I'm good.
- 真的  - 嗯
- Yeah?  - Yeah.
好 我为你骄傲 小子
Okay. I'm proud of you, kid.
你挽救了无数条生命
No telling how many lives you saved.
- 谢谢你 警官  - 没事
- Thanks, Sarge.  - All right.
嗨 席德
Yo, Sid!
有什么我能效劳的吗 丹尼
What can I do for you, Danny?
- 你是来这儿观光的吗  - 你懂的
- You just here sightseeing?  - Ah, you know,
我抵抗不了这道拱门的诱惑
I couldn't resist this view of the arch.
- 确实不错  - 是啊 你知道还有谁
- Nice view.  - Yeah. Well, you know who else
- 也抗拒不了这景观吗  - 媒体
- isn't gonna be able to resist it?  - The media?
没错 够精明 席德
That's right. Sharp as a tack, Sid.
媒体会对此大做文章的
The press is gonna have a field day with this.
那我还是赶紧回去工作吧
Well, I guess I better get to work, then.
是啊 这个家伙是什么来头
Yeah. What's this thug's story?
我弟弟除掉了他
How big a hero is
会有多风光啊
my kid brother for taking him out?
他叫盖文・布莱恩特 家住高档社区
Name is Gavin Bryant. Swanky address.
天网恢恢啊
Well, crime pays.
- 没犯罪记录  - 不会吧
- No criminal record.  - Really?
他枪里总不至于装的是橡皮糖吧
Well, I don't think his gun shoots gumdrops and lollipops.
好吧 他有个满仓的弹夹
Well, he had a fully loaded magazine,
但没有上膛 枪擦得锃亮
but nothing in the chamber; gun is clean as a whistle.
看起来最近应该没开过枪
Doesn't look like it's been fired recently.
好吧 没开过枪
Well, just because he didn't fire it
并不代表他没用它犯过罪
doesn't he didn't use it to commit a crime.
检查下这一地区有没有过其它报警电话
Check the SPRINT System for other 911 calls in the area?
谢谢提醒 丹尼
Oh, thanks for the tip, Danny--
我仅仅当了十年刑警而已
I only been a detective ten years.
我查过了 没发现
I checked; nothing popped.
好吧 你能继续调查吗
All right, can you just keep looking?
这事儿可是事关我弟弟 好吗
This is my kid brother we're talking about here, all right?
这家伙招来了个警察 他不可能是清白的
This guy drew down on a cop; there's no way he's clean.
谢谢了
Thanks.
多亏了附近群众的合作
And thanks to the cooperation of the neighborhood,
所有劫匪都被逮捕了
all the looters were apprehended.
有什么问题吗
Questions?
局长
Commissioner,
华盛顿广场公园枪击案有什么最新进展吗
any update on the Washington Square Park shooting?
谢谢 海伦
Thank you, Helen.
我接下来正要讲这件事
That was my next item.
持枪者名叫盖文・布莱恩特 是名收入不错
The gunman, Gavin Bryant, was gainfully employed
的企业高管猎头
as a corporate headhunter.
已婚并有两个小孩子
Married with two young children,
还是一名教会活跃份子
active in his church.
他的邻居和同事
The neighbors and coworkers
对此都感到非常震惊
that we've spoken to expressed shock.
谁都没想到会发生这样的事
None of them saw this coming.
他的动机目前还不明确
His motive is not yet known,
但调查仍在进行中
but the investigation is still ongoing.
有市民在交火中受伤吗
Were any civilians injured in the crossfire?
没有
Not one.
难以想象 鉴于当时人数之众
Miraculous, given the size of the crowd.
警长 有传言说涉案的警官是你的儿子
Commissioner, can you confirm the rumor
你能证实一下这件事吗
that the officer involved is your son?
据我所知 持枪者并没有开枪
I understand the gunman didn't fire a single shot.
为什么你的儿子不用电击枪制服他
Why didn't your son just Taser him?
嗯 首先 乔纳森
Well, first of all, Jonathan,
着装警员不会携带有前科犯人的文件资料
uniform officers do not carry CED's.
也许他们应该带
Well, maybe they should.
难道这就是纽约警局对付
So is this the NYPD's official policy
精神病患者的方式吗
for dealing with the mentally ill?
持枪者并没有前科
The gunman had no history of...
那是不可知的
That was unknowable.
他就是一个持枪者
He was a man
众多无辜百姓生命处于险境
with a gun, and lives were at stake.
你儿子是否尝试击落他手中枪
Did your son even try to... shoot the gun out of his hand?
你问到的警官
The officer in question
严格遵守了警方制度
was adhering to department policy,
那就是 当情况需要时
that is, to use deadly physical force
应当采取致命的武力措施
when the situation requires,
完全符合本案的情况
which it did in this instance.
我局所有警员受训时有关开火的规定
And all my officers are trained to shoot
是以解除险情为目的 并非致命
until the threat is eliminated, not to kill.
那问题就是你儿子枪法也太准了吧
So the problem was your son is too good a shot.
好吧
All right.
让我们假设一下
Let's just say...
持枪者没有瞄准那群学校的孩子们
that the gunman wasn't aiming at a group of schoolchildren,
而是瞄准你 在他扣动扳机之前
but at you-- you have a second
你只有一秒钟时间 你会怎样做
before he pulls the trigger. What do you do?
嗯 首先
Well, first of all...
太迟了 你已经死了
Too late. You're dead.
呃 澄清一下 这只是
Uh, to be clear, the commissioner
局长的假设而已
was speaking hypothetically.
那么 我能尽快见到医生吗
So, do I get to see the doc anytime soon?
听丹尼的意思 你在这说话还算好使的
Danny led me to believe you had some pull around here.
在我给你检查的时候你安静点 好吗
You need to be quiet while I get a reading, okay?
你知道的 我检查完你要害部位后医生就会来
You know, the doc'll be in as soon as I check your vitals.
好了
Okay.
你感觉如何
So, how you feeling?
很好
Fine.
- 是吗 - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
你的血压看起来不是那么回事
Well, your blood pressure says differently.
已经过高压临界值了
It's through the roof.
是啊 怪不得我
Yeah, that's on account of this ringing
耳朵里有嗡嗡声 挺烦人的
in my ear-- it's a little annoying.
是开枪后才开始的吗
That start after the shooting?
是的
Yeah.
就是耳鸣
Well, that's tinnitus.
枪击后这种现象很普遍
That's common with gunshots.
不是我幻想的就好
I'm not imagining it.
不是 我没有说是你幻想的
No, I didn't say you were imagining it.
我只是说 你不必担心
I'm just saying that... you don't need to worry,
它会自行消失的
it'll go away on its own.
那么这些都是浪费时间了 是吧
Then this was all a waste of time, right?
当然不是
No, it's not...
坐下 我还没检查完
Sit down, I'm not done with you.
你知道吗 你的症状
You know what, what you went through
是属于创伤性的
was a traumatic thing.
对谁都一样 看着我
For anyone. Look at me.
丹尼也经常卷入枪击案中 不止一次
Danny's been involved in shootings; more than one.
他也经常像我这样倍受关照吗
Does he usually get this pity party?
这不是关照你 吉米
This is not a pity party, Jamie.
你知道吗 如果你认为那些症状
And you know what, if you think all that stuff
没有困扰你那男子汉大丈夫哥哥
doesn't bother your big macho brother,
那你就是一点也不了解他
then you don't know him.
我只是按受训时要求的去做
I did what I was trained to do.
我不会因为这件事一蹶不振
I'm not gonna fall apart over it.
很好
Good.
你知道么 吉米
You know, Jamie...
这种情况下的人
people in these situations,
倾向于循环经历类似于
they tend to cycle through what looks like
悲痛的五个阶段
the five stages of grief.
包括否认
There's denial,
愤怒 讨价还价 压抑
anger, bargaining, depression...
他要向孩子们开枪 琳
Yeah, he was gonna shoot some kids, Lin, so...
我不会为了这家伙感到悲痛
I'm not gonna grieve over this guy.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I was saying.
- 你知道什么能帮我吗  - 什么
- You know what would help me? - What's that?
就是你去把医生叫来
If you could just go and get the doc,
好让这一切都快点结束
so that I could get this over with.
好吧
Okay.
我有十个目击者
I got ten witnesses
看到你用台球杆猛击那人的头部
saw you bash this guy's head in with a pool cue.
现在保持沉默对你毫无益处
There's no upside to you clamming up now.
你不明白我的米兰达权利吗
What part of my Miranda rights do you not understand?
喂
Yes!
是我 方便说话吗
It's me. Can you talk?
等一下
Hold on.
你还继续保持沉默吗
You still asserting your right to remain silent?
好 很好 好好跟这儿呆着吧 你个精神病
Yeah. Good, enjoy your stay, psycho.
- 你说什么  - 没有 不是说你
- Excuse me? - No, not you.
什么事
What is it?
关于你弟弟的
It's your brother.
你见过他了 是吧
You saw him, right?
是的 他很好
Yeah, he's good.
的确
Exactly.
怎么好又变成坏事了 琳达
Why is good bad, Linda?
他心理承受这案子的情况还不正常
He's not processing this in a healthy way.
他还处在否认阶段
He's in denial.
喂 慢着 好吗
Whoa, slow down, okay?
这案子才刚发生 他可能还处在惊吓中
This just happened; he's probably still in shock.
相信我 等他想通了 他会感觉到的
Believe me, when it hits him, he's gonna feel it.
好吧 嗯 现在新闻上也在报道
Yeah, well, now they're talking on the news
好像这个持枪者是个好人
like the gunman is this good guy.
我的意思是 这对他没什么好处
I mean, that can't be helping.
宝贝 相信我 一切都会好起来的
Babe, I'm telling you, everything's gonna be fine.
听着 我得挂了
Look, I got to go.
好的 爱你
All right, love you.
我更爱你
Love you more.
什么风把你吹来了 席德
What brings you down here, Sid?
礼节性拜访
A courtesy call.
我想你可以在新闻播出这件事
I thought you might want to give your brother a heads-up
之前给你弟弟提个醒
before this hit the news.
提什么醒
Heads-up about what?
我弟弟没做什么错事
My brother didn't do anything off-base.
他是没做错事 但这案情有些离奇了
He didn't, but the case took a bit of a weird turn.
嗯 你想让我猜吗
Well, are you gonna make me guess?
他们调出了原来的911电话记录
They pulled the initial 911 call.
举报者没报名就挂断了电话
Caller hung up without giving his name.
你们做了反向追踪吧
And you did a reverse look-up.
好吧 我知道这件事不止如此
Okay, I knew there was more to this.
那又怎样 举报者跟
So what? The caller's got
盖文・布莱恩特有关系吗
a connection to Gavin Bryant?
也可以这么说
You might say that.
干嘛啊 丹尼
What the hell, Danny?
非得让我向法院对你申请禁令吗
I have to take out a restraining order against you?
你感觉如何 小子
How you doing, kid?
在看到你的大长脸之前都很好 怎么了
All right till I saw the sour look on your face. What's up?
他们追踪到了最初拨打911电话的人
They tracked down the guy who made the initial 911 call.
就是我出警时那个报案人吧 对吧
The one I responded to, yeah?
对 电话是从盖文・布莱恩特的手机里挂的
Yeah. The call came from Gavin Bryant's cell phone.
他自己打的报案电话
He made the call himself.
不可能
That's impossible.
我向他开枪时他身上没有电话
He didn't have a phone on him when I shot him.
我知道 但是我们查看过
I know he didn't, but we checked
公园的安保录像
the security footage in the park.
我们看到盖文在拨打完911电话后立即
We got Gavin chucking his cell phone in the trash
就把他的手机丢到垃圾箱里了
seconds after the 911 call was logged.
他为什么要举报自己
Why would he report himself?
我不明白
I don't...
像他这样的精神状况
A guy in his state of mind,
没人知道他在想什么
there's no telling what he was thinking.
你在说什么 丹尼
What are you talking about, Danny?
他是哪样的精神状况
What state of mind was he in?
看样子
It looks like
他借警察之手 自杀了
he committed suicide... by cop.
自杀
Suicide?
我就是那个替他开枪的倒霉警察
I'm the sucker that he conned into doing it for him.
- 你是  - 布莱恩特夫人吗
- Yes? - Mrs. Bryant?
不是 我会告诉她你来了
No. I'll let her know you're here.
你是
Your name?
吉米
Jamie.
警官吉米・雷根
Officer Jamie Reagan.
你他妈来这儿干嘛
What the hell are you doing here?
康妮
Connie.
让他进来
Let him in.
亚历克斯 亲爱的
Alex, honey,
我需要你看一会你的小妹妹
I'm gonna need you to look after your little sister
没问题吧
for a while, okay?
我们可以在这里谈
We can talk in here.
谢谢
Thank you.
请节哀顺变
I'm so sorry for your loss.
告诉我当时是怎么回事
Tell me why it happened.
为什么你杀了我丈夫
Why did you kill my husband?
我也希望我能给你一个合理的理由
I wish I could make some sense of it for you.
我们的婚姻很稳固
Our marriage was solid.
他的业务也是蒸蒸日上
His business was never better.
他不会自杀
He was not suicidal.
你的丈夫当时很狂躁
Your husband was distraught.
他酗酒么
Had he been drinking?
他已经戒酒15年了
He was 15 years sober.
最近有什么情况么
Had something happened recently?
为什么他
Why was he...
为什么他随身带着枪
Why was he carrying a gun?
几周前他在一处治安不好的地方
He did volunteer work a few weeks ago
参加了一个志愿者活动
in a sketchy neighborhood.
也许他带枪是为了防身
Maybe he had it for protection.
有人威胁过他么
Had someone threatened him?
别说了
Stop.
我以为你过来是为了帮我弄出究竟
I thought you came here to help me understand.
原来你只是要找自己的答案
You just want answers for yourself.
我绝对不想让你更难过
The last thing I meant to do was upset you more.
你来这不就是希望我告诉你我丈夫是个恶棍
You came here expecting me to say my husband was a monster
这样你就可以对他死心安吗
so you could feel better about killing him.
抱歉 女士 我这就走
I'm sorry, ma'am. I'll go.
你夺走我们家顶梁柱的生命
You killed a wonderful husband and father.
你不会知道这对我意味着什么
You have no idea what you took from me.
艾琳 你还在这里
Erin, you're still here.
你的执着一向是我最佩服的地方
Your tenacity is one of the things
不过我饭局要迟到了
I admire most about you, but I'm late for dinner.
你为什么这么害怕作证呢
Why were you afraid to testify?
咱们到这边来说吧
Why don't we talk over here?
你是我的关键证人
You're my key witness.
陪审员已经宣誓就职了
The jury's already been sworn in.
如果你明天不露面 我们会触犯一案不能双审条例
If you don't show up tomorrow, double jeopardy attaches.
莱恩将无罪释放
Ryan walks free.
告诉我你不是这么打算的
Tell me that is not your plan.
艾琳 这事非常复杂
Erin, this is very complicated,
而且今年也是我的竞选年
and it's an election year for me.
所以这次你不适合
So it's not a good time for you
上庭宣誓答辩吗
To answer questions under oath?
并不是说我有什么见不得人的东西
Not that I have anything to hide.
但我的线人说被告打算把
But my sources say that the defense plans
这一切全都推到我身上来
To turn this whole thing on me.
怎么推
How?
他们会说莱恩拿的那些
By claiming that the money
钱是私下里用来
That Ryan took was an under-the-table payoff
给我收买选票的报酬
To implement voter fraud.
有这么回事吗
Is there anything to that?
艾琳 你怎么能这么问我
Erin, how could you ask me that?
听着 在法庭上我能保护你
Look, I can protect you in court,
但你要告诉我所有他们有可能
but you need to tell me anything
拿来攻击你的事情这样我才能先做好准备
they can throw at you, so I can get ahead of it.
艾琳 你可以随便问
Well, Erin, you can ask me anything you like.
我没什么好隐瞒的
I have nothing to hide.
现在你可不该躲着我 小子
It's not the time for you be ducking me, kid.
你可别忘了 我是你唯一的哥
In case you forgot, I'm the only brother you got.
我现在只求你让我一个人静静 丹尼
I need you to leave me alone right now, Danny.
拜托 我以为我们已经过了这个阶段了
Come on, I thought we went over this already.
嘿 你到底怎么回事啊
Hey, what's going on with you?
喂
Huh?
那个寡妇说盖文已经戒酒15年了
The widow said that Gavin was sober 15 years,
但是当时他看起来好像醉了或者嗨了似的
but he seemed drunk or high or something to me.
是啊 这是案子当时的情况
Yeah, that's what's going on with the case.
我是问你到底怎么回事
I said what's going on with you?
- 你真的想知道吗 - 是啊
- You really want to know? - Yeah.
我又生气又沮丧
I-I'm angry and I'm frustrated.
我不再确定我是否适合做一个警察
I'm not sure I'm fit to be a cop anymore.
拜托 你和任何一个我认识的警察一样适合
Oh, come on, you're as fit to be a cop as any cop I know.
万一下一次 因为这次的情况
What if the next time, because of how this went down,
我犹豫了 导致一个无辜的路人被杀了呢
I hesitate and an innocent bystander gets killed?
你不会让那种情况发生的
You won't let that happen.
你又不知道
You don't know that.
我当然知道
Yes, I do.
你那一枪干净利落
Look, it was a clean shoot.
嘿
Hey.
听着 我也遇到过你的情形 好吗
Look, I've been where you are, okay?
是这个未解之谜让我们抓狂
It's the unanswered questions that are driving you nuts.
我们不会再找到更多的答案了 对吧
Well, we're not getting any more answers, are we?
谁说的
Says who?
这案子已经被定为正当防卫杀人了
It's already been ruled a justifiable homicide.
调查已经结束
The investigation is over.
纽约警局不会在意一个男人自杀的原因
NYPD doesn't care why a guy killed himself.
好吧 那我们更有理由去
Okay, well, that's all the more reason
查个水落石出了
someone should get to the bottom of it.
可是我暂时只能做文案
Yeah, well, I'm stuck behind a desk.
我倒是想做些什么 但不可以
I'd do something, but I can't.
你是不可以 但我行
Maybe you can't, but I can.
我有私人的时间
I got some personal time.
让我花些日子好好查查 好吗
Let me take a few days and do some sniffing around, all right?
真的吗
Yeah?
真的
Yeah.
好的 去做吧
Okay, do it.
雷根警官
Detective Reagan,
你刚刚错过了布莱恩特的尸检
you just missed the Bryant autopsy.
好吧 其实我也从来都没
Yeah, well, never really interested
兴趣看现场尸检
in seeing the actual autopsy.
我只对结果感兴趣
Just interested in seeing the results.
是啊
Mm.
怎么回事 这人有什么不治之症么
What happened? This guy have a terminal illness or something?
除了心室上的
Aside from the hemorrhagic wound track
穿透性伤口以外 他很健康啊
through the cardiac ventricle, he was a fit specimen.
所以没什么不寻常的了？
So nothing was out of place.
就是最近的一根趾骨是短指
Just the proximal phalanx of his fifth phalange.
什么
What?
他有一根小指骨折了
He had a fractured pinky finger.
真的么
Really?
像让别人弄断了的一样吗
Consistent like with, uh, somebody breaking it?
比如他债主打断的吗
Like somebody he owed money to?
更像是他打别人打断的
More consistent with him having thrown a punch.
好吧 那毒检呢
All right, what about the tox screen?
有什么结果吗
Anything show up there?
呃 他的血液酒精含量是0.07
Uh, his blood alcohol was .07.
0.07
.07?
那寡妇说他戒酒了
The widow said he was on the wagon.
看来他临终前喝了杯上路酒
Guess he had one for the road.
我回来了 不知道为什么
Here I am; don't know why.
我没打算把你叫到十四楼上
Well, I wasn't about to have you up to the 14th floor.
如果你想喝 那里有咖啡
There's some coffee there, if you want it.
你最近怎么样
So how you holding up?
还好
Okay.
真的假的
Really?
你从事这份工作时
You sign up for the job,
你就知道你有可能要对人开枪的
you know you might have to shoot someone.
95%的警察在他们一生的
95% of the cops go their whole career
工作生涯中都没有在射击场外开过枪
without firing their weapon outside the range.
剩下了5%的警察
Of the five percent that are left,
有多少人第一次开枪就杀了人
how many shot first and killed the guy?
这我不知道
That I do not know.
就是刚刚 咱们警员发生一起误杀
A while ago, we had that bad shooting.
一位母亲失去了儿子
A woman lost her son.
他没做什么错事
He didn't do anything wrong.
他只是在错误的时间出现在了错误的地点
He was just in the wrong place at the wrong time.
我去看她
I went to see her.
我希望她知道我理解
I wanted her to know that I understood
失去一个孩子的感觉
what it was like to lose a child.
那是个错误
It was a mistake.
没起到一点帮助
It didn't help.
过了一会 我渐渐意识到
With time, I've come to realize
相对于安慰她 更像是在安慰我自己
that it was, well, more for my own consolation than hers.
我要说两点
Two things.
你这次不是误杀
This wasn't a bad shooting,
去看那个女人是一个错误
and it was a mistake to go see that woman.
那我该怎么做
What was I supposed to do?
你没有想要通过警局或者
You didn't think to notify the department or run it
警员慈善协会律师来处理么
by your PBA attorney?
她丈夫的死
I'm responsible...
我负有责任
for her husband's death.
你对那些没被他夺去的生命也负有责任
You're also responsible for the lives he didn't take.
事情已然至此
Don't make this any harder on yourself
就不要再逼自己了
than it already is.
说着容易做起来难啊
That's easier said than done.
听我说
Listen...
你正在经历的这些事
There's nothing you're going through,
你可能犯的错
no mistake you can make,
我都遇到过 也经历过
that I haven't already been there, done that.
我知道你现在听不进去
And I know you're not hearing too well right now,
但是别一人承担
but don't try to carry this alone.
那样做很傻
It's a fool's errand,
而你一点也不傻
and you're anything but.
你和他共事九年了吧 你知道
You worked with him for nine years-- you have any idea
他为什么又酒瘾复发了吗
what might've lead to him falling off the wagon?
不可能啊 这工作强度很高的
It never happened, and this is a high-stress business.
哦 是吗 那这个
Oh, yeah-- exactly what is it that
呃 企业猎头到底是干嘛的
a, uh, corporate headhunter does, anyway?
布莱恩特先生受雇于一些世界五百强公司
Mr. Bryant was retained by several Fortune 500 companies
他为这些公司招聘高管
to recruit high-level executives for them.
以现在的经济形势 他还能靠寻找乐意上班的人挣钱吗
In this economy, he's paid to find people willing to work?
佣金是被录用者首年收入的33%
33% of the hire's first-year income.
也许他确实还有些别的招儿挣钱
So maybe he did have something to live for anyway.
他可是个好人
He was a good man.
是啊 他也许是个好人但他最近
Yeah, well, he was a good man but he punched
可一拳打别人脸上了
someone in the face recently.
和他争业务的猎头当中有没有人
Any of his rival headhunters show up
眼眶青了或者嘴唇肿了的
with a black eye or a fat lip?
布莱恩特先生从不使用暴力
Mr. Bryant was never violent.
他打人时把小指伤了
He broke his pinky on somebody.
招聘会上有时会发生这种事
That happened somehow at Job Fair.
招聘会是什么
What is Job Fair?
他们会教一些面试技巧
They teach interview skills.
就是为那些不幸之士与其未来雇主牵手
Match up prospective employers with the down-on-their-luck.
布莱恩特先生两周前做个讲座
Mr. Bryant taught a seminar two weeks ago.
好吧 那他从讲座回来时
Right, and he came back from that seminar
小指伤了吧
with a broken pinky.
你还知道这次事后有其它什么后果吗
Any other fallout from this event that you know of?
有个参加了讲座的人来过这
One of the participants showed up here.
布莱恩特先生看着不太高兴 但他还是见了这个人
Mr. Bryant didn't seem too happy about it, but he did see him.
是么
Uh-huh.
然后呢
And?
那个男士的眼眶就青了
The gentleman had a black eye.
他眼眶就青
He had a black...
我需要这人的联系方式
I'm gonna need the guy's contact info.
他来过几次电话
He called several times.
泰勒・格林尼 没有回拨的号码
Tyler Greene-- no call-back number.
好 算他倒霉
Right, on account of he was down on his luck.
麻烦你把他名字给我
Write the name down, please.
盖文的讲座很失败
Gavin's seminar was a fiasco.
非常糟糕的那种
Worst case of flop-sweats ever.
呃 有听众的反馈吗
Any, uh, feedback from the audience?
尤其是一个叫泰勒・格林尼的
Specifically from a Tyler Greene?
我在想盖文为什么会那么紧张
Well, I had wondered if that's what made Gavin so nervous,
难道因为前排坐的是他以前的室友么
having his old roommate in the front row.
你刚说什么
Back up.
什么时候大神盖文
When were Gavin the big shot
和无家可归的泰勒・格林尼成为室友的
and Tyler Greene the homeless guy roommates?
他在麻省理工念书的第一年
His freshman year MIT.
泰勒在麻省理工念书吗
Tyler went to MIT?
是啊 至少我贴盖文的传单时
Yeah, at least that's what Tyler told me
泰勒是这么跟我说的
when I posted Gavin's flyer.
对于这个泰勒・格林尼你还了解多少
What else you know about this Tyler Greene?
他以前是个瘾君子 今年洗心革面
He's a former drug addict who showed up this year
决心改变自己的生活
clean and sober, determined to turn his life around.
好的 那你知道我上哪儿能找到他吗
Okay. You know how I can get in touch with this guy?
他 呃
Yeah, he's, uh...
他就在那边呢
he's right over there.
让我猜猜 眼圈已经青了两周那位
Let me guess-- the guy with the two-week-old shiner.
- 泰勒・格林尼  - 我什么都没干
- Tyler Greene. - I didn't do anything.
嘿 冷静点 冷静点
Hey, take it easy, take it easy.
如果我要逮捕你 我早就干了
If I was gonna arrest you, I would've done it already.
放松点
Relax.
身上带什么了吗
Anything on you?
- 有针头或者尖锐物品吗  - 没有
- Any needles or anything sharp? - No.
关于你的前室友我有些问题要问你
Need to ask you some questions about your ex-roommate.
转过来
Turn around.
我和那事没关系呀
I have nothing to do with that.
是么
Really?
你和什么事没关系呀
You had nothing to do with what?
把盖文逼到绝境的事吗
With what pushed Gavin over the edge?
从大学那会我就没见过他了
I hadn't seen him since college.
那你们兄弟会的握手方式
So what is your fraternity handshake--
就是在眼睛上来一拳吗
a punch in the eye?
他打了你 为什么
He did that to you-- why?
我们只是闹着玩的
We were just horsing around.
是么 你知道我怎么看这事吗
Really? You know what I think?
我觉得是你做了什么事才把他逼死了
I think you did something to drive him to his death.
不是的
No...
你要去哪
Where you going?
你说你没有逮捕我
You said I wasn't under arrest.
那就是说我可以走了 不对吗
That means I'm free to go, right?
是的 严格来说是
Yeah, technically.
我很抱歉
Well, I'm sorry.
你抱歉什么 泰勒
What are you sorry about, Tyler?
我真的很想知道
'Cause I'd really like to know.
盖文的死
Gavin's dead.
就让他安息吧
Just... let him rest in peace.
他说让他安息是什么意思
What did he mean "Just let him rest in peace"?
这个泰勒是我们唯一的线索了
This guy Tyler is our only lead.
你怎么就把他放了
How come you let him go?
我必须放了他
I had to let him go.
人家也没犯罪 你想让我怎么做
Guy didn't commit a crime-- what do you want me to do?
第十二区分局 雷根警官 您需要什么帮助吗
12th Precinct, Officer Reagan-- how can I help you?
马上给你接通
I'll connect you.
当你表明身份时他就跑了
The guy fled when you identified yourself.
他不可能跟这事没关系
No way he's right.
吉米 我不能以官方身份出现在那 知道吗
Jamie, I wasn't there in an official capacity, okay?
所以就算我想抓这人 我也不能抓
So even if I wanted to arrest the guy, I couldn't.
而且 咱们想在他找律师前
Besides, the idea is to get the guy to talk
先让他交待
before he lawyers up.
我得和这人谈谈
I need to talk to this guy.
绝对不行 你不能和他谈
Absolutely not-- you're not talking to him.
第十二辖区 雷根警官 您需要什么帮助吗
12th Precinct, Officer Reagan-- how can I help you?
是的 我会派一组警员过去
Yeah, I'll send a unit right over
以打骚扰电话的罪名逮捕你
to arrest you for making nuisance calls.
有女士报警说一个十岁大的孩子不肯铺床
Lady calls to report a ten-year- old for not making her bed.
我该怎么办 去崩了她吗
What am I supposed to do-- go shoot her?
你知道吗 他不适合做公关的 警官
You know, PR may not be his true calling, Sarge.
你没有其他更好的地儿去了是吗 丹尼
You don't have anywhere better to be, Danny, huh?
其实我正准备走了 警官
Actually I was just leaving, Sarge.
如果我跟你在这混时间长了
If I hang around here with you too long,
没准我就被纸把手割了
I might get a paper cut.
回头再跟你聊
I'll talk to you later.
听着
Listen...
开枪杀人后 规定你必须
after a fatal shooting, it's mandatory
去见警局心理医生
to see a department shrink.
你得去
You need to do that.
马上
Now.
明白了吗
Okay?
这笔资金的预期目的是什么
What was the intended purpose of the funds in question?
这笔资金是指定用于一个
The fund was earmarked for a program
防范贿选项目的
to safeguard against voter fraud.
这个问题很实际吗
Is that an actual problem?
在我第一轮选举时 有人针对某个
Well, my first election, a targeted a group
经济弱势的选民群体
of economically downtrodden constituents
恶意使其反感投票结果
were wrongly turned away from the polls.
我反对
Objection.
理由 斯科尼克先生
On what grounds, Mr. Skolnick?
与本案无关
Relevance?
反对无效
Overruled.
这笔资金就是为了防止
The fund was to prevent that
再发生类似事件
from ever happening again.
那么由谁负责这个项目呢
And who was in charge of this program?
被告人 瑞恩・迈克劳林
The defendant, Ryan McLaughlin.
我没有其他问题了
No further questions.
辩方还要盘问证人吗
Does the defense wish to cross-examine the witness?
是的 法官大人
Extensively, Your Honor.
提醒下 您可是宣过誓的 市长先生
I remind you, you're under oath, Mr. Mayor.
这些钱不会只是为了当做支付资金
Weren't these funds just a payoff for implementing...
我反对
Objection.
斯科尼克先生
Mr. Skolnick!
- 只是在  - 有异议
- only after... - Argumentative.
律师先生
Counselor!
你要把我的客户置于死地
You threw my client under the bus.
这是骚扰证人
Badgering the witness.
斯科尼克先生 坐下
Mr. Skolnick, sit down!
反对有效
Sustained.
证人不是在接受审判 辩方显然
The witness is not on trial, Defense clearly doesn't
站不住脚
have a leg to stand on.
雷根女士 我已经认定了你的反对有效
Ms. Reagan, I already sustained your objections.
现在是周五下午了
It's Friday afternoon.
也应该让评审团走了
I think we should let the jury go.
你不能与任何人讨论此案
You are not to discuss this case.
市长先生
Mr. Mayor?
期待与您
I expect that we will see you
在周一早上的最终庭审上见面
for finish cross-examination Monday morning?
9点半准时开始
9:30 sharp.
休庭
Court is adjourned.
谢谢你反应这么及时
I appreciate you shutting him down so quickly.
他准备在周一的时候再次对我猛攻
He's gonna have another crack at me on Monday.
他不会再揪着那些问题不放的
Not on that line of questioning, he isn't.
艾琳
Erin?
说曹操曹操就到
Speak of the devil.
我认为你不止隐瞒证据
I thought you were above withholding evidence.
我会花一整个周末的时间来起草
I'm gonna spend the weekend drafting
一项提案来制裁你
a motion against you for sanctions.
制裁我什么
Sanctions for what?
你才应该因当在审案例的证人
And you should be brought up on sanctions for discussing
面讨论案情被制裁
this case in front of a witness that's still on the stand.
你不该隐瞒开脱罪责证据的 艾琳
You shouldn't withhold exculpatory evidence, Erin.
他什么意思
Do you know what he's talking about?
我不知道
I have no idea.
没人会在无证据支持的情况下
You don't file sanctions against an ADA
提出制裁助理地区检察官的
with nothing to back it up.
艾琳 他在虚张声势
Erin, he's bluffing.
好吧 如果他真有哪怕
Okay, but if he has found evidence
一点点我开脱罪责证据 而且他又说服
that's even remotely exculpatory, and he convinces
法官我是明知故犯 那我可就要被取消从业资格了
the judge that I knew about it, I could be disbarred.
艾琳 我向你保证
Erin, I promise you,
你就放一百个心吧 没事的
you have absolutely nothing to worry about.
我还以为有个沙发躺躺
I thought I'd have to lie down on a couch.
喔 那可太贵了 政府经费不允许
Oh, we can't afford those on a government budget.
不过如果你想坐的话 就坐吧
You can take a seat, though, if you like.
得 这枪击案子的故事
Great, I get to tell my shooting story
我都快讲烂了
for the hundredth time.
不 没必要
No, you don't have to do that.
这只是创伤报告
This is a trauma debriefing.
不是心理评估
It's not a psych evaluation.
你现在说的一切都是保密的 也不会有任何记录的
Everything you say here is confidential and off the record.
我不会记笔录 也不会跟
I'm not taking notes, I'm not reporting
警局报告
back to the department.
好吧 那为啥还是强制的
Right, so why is it mandatory then?
这只是个预防性的措施
It's a preventative service.
防止啥
Preventing what?
创伤后精神紧张性障碍
Post-traumatic stress disorder.
我没有症状
Yeah, I don't have that.
大多数有你这种经历的人都会出现
Most people experience low to moderate symptoms
低度至中度症状
after an incident like this.
他们通常需要几周的时间来缓解
They usually resolve themselves in a couple of weeks.
我只是告诉你些注意事项
This is just to let you know what to look out for.
我可没有创伤后紧张性精神障碍
Door slams, you jump out of your skin-- I don't have PTSD.
还有 比较易怒
Also, irritability.
好吧 我确实有点
Yeah, okay, I have a little bit of that.
头疼啊 心跳过速啊
Headaches, rapid heart rate.
思想受干扰
Intrusive thoughts.
事故发生时的情形在脑子里面反复循环
Reliving the experience over and over in your head,
使劲想改变结果
trying to change the outcome.
最后一个 我有
The last one, I do that.
那块猪排你是不是不吃了
You gonna let that pork chop go to waste?
你要是不吃的话 就给我吧
'Cause if you are, you know, I'll take it off your hands.
- 谢谢 - 吉米叔叔
- Thank you. - Uncle Jamie,
瑞奇・沙利文要我谢谢你救了他一命
Richie Sullivan wanted me to thank you for saving his life.
谁是瑞奇・沙利文
Who's Richie Sullivan?
我们跆拳道课的同学
A guy in our Tae Kwon Do class.
他在去我们学校实地考查的时候
He was on our school field trip
被人用枪指着
and a man pointed a gun right at him.
你救了他们
You saved them.
瑞奇本来就没啥危险 兄弟
Richie was never in any real danger, bud.
跟瑞奇・沙利文说 你叔叔说不客气
Tell Richie Sullivan your uncle said he's welcome.
跆拳道 哈
Tae Kwon Do, huh?
你是怎么被他们说服的 琳达阿姨
How'd you let them talk you into that one, Aunt Linda?
他们说这是个需要高度集中精神且纪律严明的运动
Well, they sold me on the focus and discipline,
但是就我目测的结果 就是各种脚踢
but all I've seen so far is a lot of kicking.
还有各种拳打
And punching
和各种攻击
and striking.
他一般会挠挠后脑勺
He scratches the back of his head
在他忽悠你的时候
when he's bluffing.
谁啊
Who?
市长呗 他有这个特点
The mayor-- he has a tell.
每次他在忽悠的你时候 总会挠挠后脑勺
He scratches the back of his head when he's bluffing.
我们玩牌的时候发现他这个毛病 果断飞掉他
Picked it up in a poker game-- cleaned him out.
- 很高兴有所了解 - 嗯哼
- That's good to know. - Mm-hmm.
他是个政客 所以他头都被挠破了吧
He's a politician, he must do a lot of scratching.
你跟神奇的格蕾丝见过了 小子
Is it true you drew Amazing Grace, kid?
谁是神奇的格蕾丝
Who's Amazing Grace?
局里的心理医生
The department shrink.
意思是说他疯了么
Does that mean he's crazy?
不是 机灵鬼 不是说他疯了
No, Wisenheimer, it doesn't mean he's crazy.
警局的制度 开枪之后 你必须得去
It's department policy-- after a shooting, you have to go.
没办法
You got no choice.
不是说去见心理医生 就说明你疯了
Well, not that seeing a shrink means you're crazy.
我在位时 可没有这套
My day, there was no department shrink.
是啊 那时候都自己扛过去直到崩溃
Yeah, guys bottled it up until they stroked out.
啊 还是原来好啊
Ah, the good old days.
我跟你 你应该逮捕泰勒的
I told you, you should've arrested Tyler.
是啊 你得
Yeah, well, and you need
在你崩溃之前放下包袱
to learn to let things go before you stroke out.
泰勒在这儿在做啥呢
Do we know what Tyler's doing here?
非法入侵 这只是个开始
Trespassing, for starters.
喂 喂 慢着 你在这呆着
Whoa, whoa, whoa-- you hang back
我看看他到底在搞什么鬼
till I find out what's going on with Tyler.
啥 你叫我在这里等
What-- you expect me to wait in the car?
我会敲碎窗户给你信号
I'll crack the window for you.
听着 你就不该来这
Look, kid, you shouldn't even be here.
我才是那个需要答案的人
I'm the one who needs answers.
我帮你找 行么 相信我
And I'm gonna get them for you, trust me.
我要进去
I'm coming in.
随你便吧
Suit yourself.
我们几个人进去把招聘会遣散了
Hey. A few of us came in to tear down the Job Fair.
泰勒来了 表现非常怪异
Tyler showed up, acting... pretty bizarre.
是么 他身上有武器么
Yeah? He got any weapons on him?
据我所知没有 不过他肯定是嗑药了
Not that I know of, but he's definitely high.
听我说 他是个好人
Look, he-he's a good guy.
不管那天你跟他说了啥
Whatever went down with you the other day
- 肯定是导火索 - 好的
- must've set him off.- All right.
我们会处理好的
We'll take care of it, okay?
你先别进来了
We need you to stay out here.
泰勒
Tyler?
抱歉
Sorry.
我们不会伤害你的
We ain't gonna hurt you.
我们只是想跟你聊聊 好么
We just came to talk, all right?
你嗑了什么 泰勒
What are you on, Tyler?
什么都磕了
Everything.
我只是 只是想他停下来 我只是想让他停下
I just, I just want it to stop. I-I want him to stop.
我想让他停下 但他死活不停 就是不停
I want him to stop, but he won't, he won't stop!
谁 谁 泰勒 盖文么 他已经死了
Who? Who, Tyler? Gavin? He's dead.
告诉我们原因
Tell us why.
一个错误
A mistake.
那就是个错误
It was a mistake.
为啥你不到后面等下 兄弟 行不
Why don't you just hang back, kid, all right?
别给自己惹麻烦
Don't get yourself in trouble.
我不会走的 丹尼
I'm not leaving, Danny.
他为啥想自杀
Why did he want to kill himself?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是吉米・雷根警官
I'm Officer Jamie Reagan.
就是你杀了盖文
You're the one who killed Gavin.
不 不 是盖文 他自作自受
No... no, Gavin brought this on himself.
你还是说说为啥他这么做吧
Why don't you tell us why he did it, okay?
我只想让他为他所做的付出代价
I just wanted him to pay for what he did.
他不应该死的
He wasn't supposed to die.
他做了啥
What did he do?
他做了什么 泰勒
What did he do, Tyler?
放松点
Take it easy.
把你的手从兜里拿出来
Get your hand out of your pocket.
嘿 把你的手从兜里拿出来
Hey, get your hand out of your pocket.
放下 把刀放下
Hey! Drop it! Hey! Drop the knife!
叫救护车
Call an ambulance!
不 你不能死在这里
No, don't you die on me!
在我传评审团进来之前
Before I have them bring the jury in,
还有任何其他的申请么
are there any applications?
请问法官大人对
Is the judge's offer
认罪的最长刑期提议是否有效
for the top count plea still open?
什么
What?
如果被告认罪接受
If the defendant would plead out
本次指控的最长刑期
at the top count of the indictment,
鉴于这是他的初犯
this being his first offense,
我仍然倾向于
I would still be inclined
建议对其判一至三年
to recommend a sentence of one to three.
与此同时
Then, at this time,
被告会承认
the defendant would like to plead guilty
三级重大窃盗罪
to grand larceny in the third degree.
为什么
Why?
有问题吗 雷根女士
Is there a problem, Ms. Reagan?
没有 我只是很意外
No, I'm just... surprised.
市长还在外面等候接受盘问
I have the mayor outside waiting to be crossed.
我们很不愿意麻烦
Well, much as we hate to inconvenience
市长阁下
His Majesty the Mayor,
被告会承认
the defendant is pleading guilty
你对他的控告
to charges you brought against him.
这就是判决 雷根女士
It's a conviction, Ms. Reagan.
接受吧
Take it.
被告现在将起立
The defendant will now stand
宣读对他的待定指控
and allocute to the pending charges against him.
你们俩碰巧就碰上了
So the two of you just happened to end up
一个你们觉得和这案子
with a guy you felt was connected
相关的人
to the case.
这几率能有多大
What are the odds?
丹尼 你看上去一直都能遇事摆平的
Danny, you always seem to land on your feet.
但有一天你可能就摆不平了
But someday you won't,
我也帮不了你
and I won't be able to help.
至少我不该帮你
At least, I shouldn't.
我明白
I understand.
我会为我的搭档把这种事解决
I would see this thing through for a partner,
我当然会为我弟弟解决
I damn well gotta see it through for my kid brother.
作为你的上司 我命令你要听从你的父亲
And as your boss, I'm ordering you to listen to your father.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
再也别去逞能了
No more going off the grid.
不过 既然我做了
Though, now that I did,
我偶然发现这个人和我跟的案子有关
I stumbled upon the guy who is legitimately my case.
到底是什么样的案子
And what case is that, exactly?
要弄清盖文到底怎么了 泰勒是关键
Tyler is the key to finding out what happened to Gavin.
吉米应该知道这个人到底要说什么
Jamie deserves to hear what this guy's got to say.
泰勒怎么样
What's Tyler's condition?
很稳定 不过他打了镇静剂 我不能跟他说话
He's stable, but he's sedated, so I can't talk to him.
你在想什么
So what are you thinking?
我在想泰勒和盖文读大学的时候
I'm thinking that something pretty heavy went down
肯定发生过大事
with Tyler and Gavin when they were back in college.
我就打电话给剑桥警方
So I put in a call to Cambridge PD
想查查发生在那个时候的悬案
to look into some cold cases from back then.
我想
I suppose...
我们能给泰勒
we could get Tyler on menacing
定个恐吓和非法携带武器罪
and criminal possession of a weapon.
这些作用都不大
There's not a lot of leverage in that.
如果碰上个接洽的法官的话
Well, with the right judge,
也许能帮你弄到张搜查令
maybe you can get a search warrant.
那要让接洽的人打电话给接洽的法官
If the right person calls the right judge.
一个字都别和局长提
Not a word of this to the commissioner.
艾琳
Erin!
你还没走啊
You're still here.
我干嘛要走
Why wouldn't I be?
怎么了
What happened?
别告诉我审讯还没结束
Don't tell me the trial was continued.
审讯结束了
No, the trial's over.
莱恩认罪了
Ryan pled out.
就是说我们赢了
So we won.
没错 对你来说可是双赢啊
Yeah, that's a win-win for you.
等我一下
Give me a second.
艾琳 我不大懂
Erin, I'm not quite sure
你的意思
what that's supposed to mean.
我不明白为什么斯科尼克
I don't know why Skolnick
要在周五那么扬言叫嚣而
would make the claims that he did on Friday
今天却急转直下认栽了
and then turn around and fall on his sword today.
原因我告诉过你的  没有无罪开脱证据
Well, I told you: because there was no exculpatory evidence.
他在虚张声势
He was bluffing.
我觉得上周末在我不知情的情况下
I think there was a backroom deal made over the weekend
有过秘密交易
that I'm not privy to.
艾琳 你说的这些我都不知道
Erin, none that I had any knowledge of.
你向我保证过 我什么都不用担心
You promised me that I had nothing to worry about,
所有的制裁威胁
and all the sanction threats that he made
就这么神奇地消失了
just magically disappeared.
好吧
Okay.
你就问我吧
Go ahead and ask me.
问你什么
Ask you what?
他们有没有
If there is anything to
中伤过我
the mud they were flinging at me.
我是这所法院的助理检察官
I am an officer of this court.
如果有人宣誓后做伪证
If there were any lies told under oath,
我有义务向上汇报
I am obligated to report them.
问吧
Ask.
有吗
Were there?
没有
No.
那就好
Good.
你好像玩的很开心啊
You look like you're having fun.
才没有 告诉我有好事了
No, but tell me I'm about to.
你执行泰勒的搜查令了
You executed Tyler's search warrant?
是啊
I did.
你怎么了 说话大喘气
What's with you and the dramatic pauses?
你抓的那个泰勒
Your guy Tyler was the recipient
接受的盖文・布莱恩特的遗书
of Gavin Bryant's suicide note.
盖文自杀后还留言了吗
Gavin left a suicide note?
有意思 上面写什么了
Well, that's beautiful. What'd it say?
你查的这些悬案里面
In your cold case files here,
有查到一个叫安娜的人吗
you find anything involving someone named Anna?
安娜
Anna. Uh...
好像有个强奸案和凶杀案里有
Maybe one in rape and one in homicide.
怎么了 遗书写什么了
Why? What does the note say?
你自己看吧
Read it for yourself.
泰勒 你说的没错
"Tyler, you were right.
我要为自己的行为付出代价 但是我不能承受
"I have to pay for what I did, but I can't face
你给我选择的惩罚
the punishment you have chosen for me."
你给他选择了什么惩罚
What punishment did you choose for him?
坐牢
Prison.
我告诉他如果我不自首 我就告发他
Told him if he didn't turn himself in, I would.
安娜当年只比我女儿现在大几岁
"Anna was just a few years older than my own daughter is now.
我夺走了她的生命
"I took her life...
我选择结束自己的生命作为交换
I choose to take my own in return."
安娜・珀塞尔
Anna Purcell.
15年前死于一场
Young girl killed in a hit-and-run
肇事逃逸
15 years ago.
肇事的是你和盖文吗
This was you and Gavin?
当时我们都磕嗨了
We were both high.
盖文坚持要开车
Gavin insisted on driving.
他撞的她
He hit her.
拖着她开了两趟街 都没停过
Dragged her two blocks, didn't even stop.
当时你怎么不告发他
Why didn't you turn him in then?
他是我的朋友
He was my friend.
他跟我说他宁愿死也不进监狱
He told me he'd rather die than go to prison.
那你就什么措施都未采取
So instead, you did nothing.
看看你的报应
And look how it turned out for you.
它毁了我的生活
It ruined my life.
它毁了很多人的生活
It ruined a lot of lives.
盖文却春风得意了
Gavin's turned out perfectly.
这不公平
It wasn't fair.
我有把枪
"I have a gun.
我会去个我家人找不到我的地方自杀
"I'll go somewhere my family won't find my body.
希望我有勇气自杀成功
"I pray I have the nerve to carry it out.
如果我还是太懦弱 杀不了自己
"If I turn out to be a coward in this as well,
我发誓会找个替代方法结束生命
I promise I'll find an alternative."
盖文找到替代方法了
Well, Gavin found his alternative, all right.
他的替代方法就是让我杀他
Yeah, his alternative was me.
我们把遗书读给他听
So we read him the suicide note
他就交待了
and he opened up about it.
没错
Yep.
吉米费了好大的精力
Though Jamie did a hell of a job
一个人把那些碎片拼起来了
putting the pieces together all by himself.
百分之十
Ten percent.
什么百分之十
What's 10%?
吉米想知道有多少警察在执勤的时候开枪
Jamie wanted to know how many cops who fired their weapon
弄出人命的
in the line of duty had a fatal result.
哦
Oh...
这个百分之十
Ten percent.
- 百分之五中的百分之十  - 没错
- 10% of the 5%.  - Yep.
他们中的三个就在这儿坐着
And three of them are sitting right here.
这样的几率有多大
What are the odds of that?
这个圈子谁都不想进来
It's not a club anyone asks to join.
没错 但我们都在这儿
Nope, but here we are.
这说明什么
What does that say about us?
也许是当本能意识到要逃离火源的时候
Maybe when basic instinct says to run away from a fire,
有些人反而会跑向火
a few run towards it.
如果他受挫折
"If he fails,
至少是尽其勇
"he at least fails daring greatly,
人们对他的评价
so that his place..""
岂能与那些冷漠 胆小 既不能领略胜利
"...shall not be with those cold and timid souls
又不能明白失败的人同日而语
who neither know victory or defeat."
愿此类事件不再发生
Here's to never again.
同愿
Here, here.
五
欢迎大家关注我们的微博@五零字幕组诚邀大家加入我们
零
字
幕
组
倾
情
奉
献
一起为美剧迷们打造更快更好的双语字幕
QQ群号:179970424